<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Onur Celep</title><link>onurcelep.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Onur Celep</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="onurcelep.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>onurcelep.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>onurcelep.github.io/about/</guid><description>Who I am? Link to heading A passionate software engineer with 10+ years of experience. A detail-oriented, communicative, adaptable engineer who specializes in analysis, design, and implementation of CI/CD and software test automation systems. Contributed development process of several high-volume and revenue software products. Interested in cloud systems, CI/CD, performance &amp;amp; automation test development areas.
My Career Link to heading Software Consultantcy Link to heading Providing technical consultancy and leadership services in CI/CD design and implementation, release management and automation, data visualization , root cause analysis, technical way of working and KPI definition, team building areas.</description></item><item><title>Contact Information</title><link>onurcelep.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>onurcelep.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Email
Book a 30 min call</description></item><item><title>Offered Services</title><link>onurcelep.github.io/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>onurcelep.github.io/services/</guid><description>Architecture Analysis and Design
Let me analyze and design a custom architecture for your software system to ensure it is efficient, scalable, and maintainable
CI/CD Implementation
Streamline your software development and delivery process with my CI/CD implementation services. I&amp;rsquo;ll set up and configure the tools and processes needed to automatically build, test, and deploy code changes.
Development tooling
Need help setting up the tools and infrastructure for your software development team?</description></item></channel></rss>